#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vi-nguyen-hothanh-tuong-b46a971b4 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

UiPath Agile Testing

Microsoft Office

#### Certifications

Chinese for HSK 2
Excel Quick Tips (2018)
Business Analysis Foundations
Agile Requirements Foundations
English for Business and
Entrepreneurship

# Vi Nguyen Ho Thanh Tuong

**Business Analyst** 

Da Nang City, Vietnam

## Summary

A girl who is always full of energy, enthusiasm and wants to spread positivity to everyone around.

An Business Analyst with a history in the information technology and services industry stands out for me. Besides, I also have experience in retail and marketing through part-time jobs when I was a student at FPT University.

## Experience

**FPT Software** 

3 years 11 months

**Business Analyst** 

August 2021 - Present (3 years 8 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

**RPA Business Analyst** 

**Business Analyst Intern** 

May 2021 - August 2021 (4 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

EduTab Academy

Marketing Staff

March 2021 - July 2021 (5 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

**FPT Education Global** 

Buddy

September 2019 - March 2020 (7 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

### Education

## FPT University

Bachelor's degree, International Business · (2018 - 2022)